zapping.com 2016-03-17

# Watch movies online for Free in zapping.com

## Privacy policy

This Privacy Policy applies to information we collect about you at zapping.com (the "Website") and zapping.com applications and how we use this information.

##### Collection of your zapping.com Information

Your "zapping.com information" includes certain technical information gathered or received when you use zapping.com. Some of the technical information that may be collected or received includes: the type of browser you are using (e.g., Netscape, Internet Explorer), the type of operating system you are using (e.g., Windows or Mac OS), CPU type, your manner of connecting to the Internet (e.g., connection speed through narrowband or broadband access); Internet protocol address; Apps Installed; information about the version of service from an affiliate that you used prior to registering with the service; other information about your geographic location; and the domain name of your Internet service provider.

While registering to use most of the zapping.com services is not required, there are a limited number of optional services (for example, saving a video list) that require an "account". Registration functionality for zapping.com is provided by the zapping.com Network. If you choose to "Register an Account", you will need to register with and provide information to zapping.com. You will then obtain a Screen Name or other credential issued by zapping.com (collectively, "Screen Name") in order to access and use these optional services, and your Screen Name and associated services account will be subject to the zapping.com Terms of Service Agreement and Privacy Practices indicated in your registration process.

##### How Your zapping.com information is Used

Your zapping.com information is used

  * to operate and improve the websites, services and offerings available through zapping.com;
  * to personalize the content provided to you;
  * to fulfill your requests for products, programs, and services;
  * to communicate with you and respond to your inquiries;
  * to conduct research about your use of zapping.com; and
  * to help offer you other products, programs, or services that may be of interest.

Your zapping.com information will not be shared with third parties unless it is necessary to fulfill a request, in other circumstances in which you have consented to the sharing of your zapping.com information, or except as described in this Privacy Policy. We may use your zapping.com information to present offers to you on behalf of business partners and advertisers. These business partners and advertisers may receive aggregate data about groups of zapping.com users, but do not receive information that personally identifies you.

If you use our communications tools to disclose information about yourself publicly (for example, by making your screen name and/or video lists publicly available), other online users may obtain access to any information you provide. The contents of your online communications, as well as other information about you as a zapping.com user, may be accessed and disclosed in response to legal process (for example, a court order, search warrant or subpoena); in other circumstances in which we believe zapping.com is being used in the commission of a crime; when we have a good faith belief that there is an emergency that poses a threat to the safety of you or another person; or when necessary either to protect our rights or property or the rights or property of our affiliated providers, or for us to render the service you have requested. We may use agents and contractors in order to help operate the service. If such agents and contractors have access to your zapping.com information, they are required to protect this information in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy by, for example, not using the information for any purpose other than to carry out the services they are performing for zapping.com.

In the event that ownership of us or the zapping.com service was to change as a result of a merger, acquisition or transfer to another company, your zapping.com information may be transferred. If such a transfer results in a material change in the use of your zapping.com information, we will provide notice about the choices you have to decline to permit such a transfer.

##### Your Choices About Your Information

If you want to change your account information (for example, your Screen Name) you will need to log onto zapping.com and access your account through the forum. Your access to your account information and choice will be governed by the zapping.com policies.

##### Cookies, Web Beacons and Similar Technologies

Cookies are text files that are placed in your computer's browser, and that can be used to help recognize you as a zapping.com user. Web beacons are small pieces of code placed on Web pages that can be used, among other things, to count the users who visit that Web page, or to deliver a cookie to the browser of a user viewing that page. You can control cookies through your browser's settings. If you reject all cookies, however, you will not be able to take advantage of certain zapping.com offerings.

We may use cookies, web beacons or similar technologies in combination with your zapping.com information to enhance and personalize your experience on zapping.com, including to operate and improve offerings through zapping.com; to help authenticate you when you use zapping.com; to remember your preferences; to present and help measure and research the effectiveness of zapping.com offerings and advertisements; and, to customize the content and advertisements provided to you through zapping.com.

zapping.com and its advertisers may use advertising network providers to help present advertisements on zapping.com. These advertising networks may use cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies on your computer in order to provide targeted advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you while visiting other Web sites. The use of cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies by ad network providers is subject to their own privacy policies. Any choices that you have about these technologies will be presented here in the event we utilize the services of any advertising network provider. Therefore, you are encouraged to return to this section periodically for updated information about advertising networks.

Third party vendors, including Google, show your ads on sites on the internet. Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to your website. Users may opt out of Google’s use of cookies by visiting the Google advertising opt-out page. (Alternatively you can opt out of a third party vendor’s use of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative opt out page.) 

We may use third-party advertising companies to collect data and/or serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, visit http://networkadvertising.org/. 

##### Security

We have established safeguards to help prevent unauthorized access to or misuse of your zapping.com information, but cannot guarantee that this information will never be disclosed in a manner inconsistent with this Privacy Policy (for example, as a result of unauthorized acts by third parties that violate applicable law or the policies of the service and its affiliated providers).

##### Special Note for Parents

zapping.com is intended for a general audience. Registration for certain services on zapping.com may not be available for children under the age of 13.

##### How to Contact Us

If you have any questions or concerns about zapping.com's Privacy Policy or its implementation, you may contact us by going to the following link: http://www.zapping.com/contact.html

##### Changes to this Privacy Policy and Additional Information

We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time, and so you should review this Policy periodically. If there are significant changes to zapping.com's information practices, you will be provided with appropriate online notice. You may be provided other privacy-related information in connection with your use of offerings from zapping.com, as well as for special features and services not described in this Policy that may be introduced in the future.
